(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To our guests,
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援 OKです
Cheering loudly is okay.
白上フブキ1stソロライブ FBKINGDOM 応援セット
Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live: FBKINGDOM Support Set
受注生産グッズ：ペンライト、タオル、缶バッジ、Tシャツ、腕章
Made-to-order goods: Penlight, towel, badge, T-shirt, wristband
受注生産グッズ：ジオラマスタンド、タペストリー、ハンカチ、ブローチ
Made-to-order goods: Diorama stand, tapestry, handkerchief, brooch
皆さまからの応援メッセージを一部ご紹介させていただきます！
Introducing some of your support messages!
FBKINGDOM ANTHEM - Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live -
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering (loudly) is OK.
白上フブキ1stソロライブ 受注生産グッズ
Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live: Made-to-order Goods
FBKINGDOM ANTHEM
- Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live -
2025.2.13(THU) PIA ARENA MM
The concert will be starting soon.
Sponsors
協賛
歌いたい曲が入っていなかった
The song I wanted to sing wasn't included.
JOYSOUND X1で歌おうぜ！
Let's sing on JOYSOUND X1!
JOYSOUND X1 Only One
JOYSOUND X1 曲数No.1
JOYSOUND X1, No. 1 in song count
AIが採点 絶賛
AI scoring, highly acclaimed
カラオケ最高！盛り上がり最高！
Karaoke is the best! The hype is the best!
歌いたい曲があるって最高！
It's the best to have songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND X1
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is ok.
白上フブキ1stソロライブ 受注生産グッズ
Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live - Made-to-order merchandise
FBKINGDOM ANTHEM - Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live -
FBKINGDOM ANTHEM
- Shirakami Fubuki 1st Solo Live -
本日は、白上フブキ 1stソロライブ
Today, at Shirakami Fubuki's 1st Solo Live
「FBKINGDOM ANTHEM」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
"FBKINGDOM ANTHEM", thank you for coming.
はい、どうも皆さん、こんわきーつ！白上フブキです！ハイ、フレンズ！
Hi everyone, kon-ba-kitsu! It's Shirakami Fubuki! Hi, friends!
わあ、たくさん盛り上がっておる！イェイイェイイェイ！
Wow, everyone's so hyped! Yay yay yay!
さてさて、ライブを最後まで楽しんでいただくために、いくつか「いい声」の白上さんがご案内させていただきます。
Now, to make sure everyone enjoys the concert until the end, a "good-voiced" Shirakami will give you a few reminders.
うっ、うっ、んんっ。
Ahem, ahem, ahem.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and the use of recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
The venue is non-smoking. Please refrain from smoking.
あ、いい声だ！
Oh, what a nice voice!
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not overdo it and notify a nearby staff member.
はーい！
Okay!
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のみなさんの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Activities such as moshing, diving, and throwing objects onto the stage are strictly prohibited, as they may disturb others or disrupt the performance.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね。
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
はーい！
Okay!
いつもの白上さんです。
Back to the usual Shirakami-san.
また、本公演は映像配信、および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、みんなが映り込む場合があるよー！
Also, cameras for video distribution and photography are in the venue, so you might be on camera!
見てる！
We're watching!
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーションなどに使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#ディアフブキングダム」です！ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
Also, the concert hashtag is "#DearFubukingdom"! Please use it to spread the hype!
おお、いい返事だ！
Oh, that's a good response!
それでは、開演までもう少しです。みんな、声出す準備できてるよな！
Now, it's almost time for the show to start. Everyone, are you ready to shout?!
フブキ！フブキ！フブキ！フブキ！フブキ！フブキ！フブキ！フブキ！
Fubuki! Fubuki! Fubuki! Fubuki! Fubuki! Fubuki! Fubuki! Fubuki!
FBKINGDOM ANTHEM
フブコンの皆さん！
Everyone at Fubukon!
準備はできてますか？
Are you ready?
Say！ Fanfare！ いきますよ！
Say! Fanfare! Here we go!
イェー！
Yeeeeaaaah!
はい！はい！
Hai! Hai!
うーー、こんこん！
Ooh, Kon-Kon!
ふー！
Fooo!
せーの！ Are you ready?
One, two! Are you ready?
ほっと一息お茶ですや
Time for a relaxing cup of tea
（はい、どうぞ！）
(Here you go!)
いつもの場所から元気にせーのでご挨拶
A cheerful greeting from the usual spot on three
（こんこん！）
(Kon-kon!)
始めましょうは
Let's get started
お喋りをしてゲームとする
Chatting and playing games
そんな毎日が愛しくて
Every day like that is precious
あれもこれも手を出したくなり勝ちです
I tend to want to try a bit of everything
歌とか成長はまだまだ恥ずかしいけど
Singing and growing is still a bit embarrassing
（ふー！）
(Fooo!)
支え合ってほら
Supporting each other, look,
届けますよこの声は
I'll send out this voice
Say！ ほらその顔上げて
Say! Come on, look up
みんなで手を取れば
If we all hold hands
Sai！ まだまだ道半ば
Sai! Still halfway there
世界を越えよう
Let's go beyond the world
Say！ ほら推し推し様
Say! Hey there, my dear fans
止まらない全力ですから
Because I'm going at full power without stopping
夢を書き換えたら
Once we've rewritten our dreams,
追いかけ続けよう
let's keep chasing them
共に鳴るファンファーレ Go!
The fanfare sounding together, Go!
イェー！
Yeah!
はい！はい！
Hai! Hai!
うーー、こんこん！
Ooh, Kon-Kon!
ふー！
Fooo!
せーの！ Go Go Let's Go!
One, two! Go Go Let's Go!
ちょっとやらかした時でも
Even when I mess up a little
（大丈夫！）
(It's okay!)
気持ち切り替えてボーッとしちゃう昼下がりは
Switching gears on a spacing-out afternoon
背伸びをして
Stretching out
お腹減らすグーもぐもぐと
Grumbling stomach, munching away
お茶の合間スコーンのおやつで
With a scone snack between cups of tea
ほい、あの子には内緒にしてほしいです
Hey, I want you to keep this a secret from her
仲間の力とお友達の皆様と
With the strength of comrades and all my friends
叶えたい想いは言葉にして
Putting the feelings I want to fulfill into words,
一つ一つ
one by one
Say！ ほらその手を上げて
Say! Come on, raise those hands
みんなで輪になれば
If we all form a circle
Sai！ まだまだ成長中
Sai! Still growing
問題ないでしょう
There shouldn't be any problem, right?
Say！ ほら明るく元気な
Say! Look, a bright and cheerful
心が取り柄ですから
Heart is my best quality
凹みがちな時も
Even when you're feeling down
輝き続けてよ
Please keep on shining
共に繋ぐアンコール
The encore we bridge together
Go! Yay!
さぶらのみんな、声全然足りないぞ！
Everyone in the kingdom, your voices aren't nearly loud enough!
まだまだ声出せるよなー！
You can still give me more, right?!
うー、Go Go Let's Go!
Uu, Go Go Let's Go!
何もかもが新しくて
Everything was so new
右も左もわからない時も
Even when I didn't know left from right
頑張れたのはみんながいたから
I was able to do my best because you were all there
一つ一つ応援が
Each and every cheer
後押しになって一歩ずつでも
Became my support, allowing me, even step by step,
私は自分らしく磨いていくフューチャー
To polish the future in my own way
答えもイメージもまだまだ手探りしても
Even if I'm still groping for answers and images
響き合ってほら世界は今きらめいて
Look, resonating together, the world is now sparkling
精いっぱいの顔を上げて
Raise your faces with all your might
みんなで手をとれば
If we all take each other's hands
最高から夢の先へ駆けだそう
Let's run from the best toward the edge of our dreams
精一杯の推し推し事も
All our dedicated fan activities
止まらない全力ですから
Because we're going full throttle without stopping
大好きな思いが溢れそうなほど
So much that my feelings of love overflow
共に繋ぐファンファーレ、Go! Yay!
The fanfare we bridge together, Go! Yay!
はい！はい！うー、ぽこん！
Hai! Hai! Uu, pokon!
うー、ぽこん！はい！はい！
Uu, pokon! Hai! Hai!
ふわふわふわふわ！イェイ！
Fuwa fuwa fuwa fuwa! Yay!
はい！はい！うー、ぽこん！
Hai! Hai! Uu, pokon!
はい！はい！はい！はい！One, two, three, Fox!!
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! One, two, three, Fox!!
イェーイ！
Yay!
皆さん、本日はフブキングダムへようこそ！
Everyone, welcome to the Fubkingdom today!
みんなの声、そして私の歌を
Your voices, and my song,
この横浜に響かせるぞ！
I'm going to make them resonate through Yokohama!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はいはいぽこん！
Hai hai pokon!
コンコンキツネ！
Kon kon kitsune!
私は白上フブキです
I am Shirakami Fubuki
お歌とお茶とゲームが大好き
I love singing, tea, and games
オタクなバーチャルキツネです
I'm an otaku virtual fox
いろんなことして毎日楽しく活動してるので
I'm active every day doing all sorts of fun things, so
フブちゃんフブさん白上皆さん、お好きに呼んでください
Fubu-chan, Fubu-san, Shirakami, everyone please call me whatever you like
動画配信お疲れ様
Good work on the video stream
生放送もお疲れ様
Good work on the live broadcast too
ひとりぼっちの朝から夜まで
From lonely mornings until night
私が傍にいます
I am by your side
はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai!
今日もどこかで、ほら笑い声響いて
Today, somewhere, look, laughter is resonating
君もいつだって明日だってウェルカムです
You're welcome anytime, even tomorrow
まだまだみんな途中
Everyone is still on their way
おっとろしすぎるときは
When things get too scary
宝物だせー！
Bring out your treasures!
泣いたって、しょげたって、大丈夫！
Even if you cry or feel down, it's okay!
笑顔で一緒に、はい！はい！はい！
With a smile, together, hai! hai! hai!
心は音に重ねて
Layering our hearts with the sound
届けましょう My Happy Day
Let's deliver "My Happy Day"
はーじまぽん！今日は何して遊びましょうか？
Hajimapon! What shall we play today?
お茶でも飲んで一息ついて今日はソロライブ？
Have some tea, take a breath, and today it's a solo live?
皆さんのこともっと知れたら私も幸せなんので
I'd be happy to get to know more about everyone, so
吊ったり買ったりアピールしたり皆さんせーのでご一緒に！
Fishing, buying, appealing... everyone together on three!
楽しくて飛び跳ねてきます
It's fun and I'm jumping around
嬉しくて打ち込んできます
I'm happy and getting into it
皆さんの傍でちょこんと
Right there by your side
私が傍にいます
I am by your side
はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai!
今日もどこかで、ほら笑い声甘いから
Today, somewhere, look, because laughter is sweet
君と誰だって明日だってウェルカムです
You and anyone else are welcome tomorrow too
待って待って成長中
Wait, wait, I'm still growing
同じ時を過ごす今が
This moment we spend together
幸せなんですよ
Is what makes me happy
泣いたって、しょげたって、大丈夫！
Even if you cry or feel down, it's okay!
笑顔で一緒に、はい！はい！はい！
With a smile, together, hai! hai! hai!
輝く色を重ねて
Layering sparkling colors
広げましょう My Brand New World
Let's expand "My Brand New World"
僕らは旅をして
We're on a journey
世界はまわって
The world keeps spinning
強まって待って待って
Getting stronger, wait, wait, wait
心は通い合わせよう
Let's connect our hearts
どこだって届けるよ
I'll reach you anywhere
私は知ってるよ
I know
誰だって繋がるよ
Anyone can connect
ここから始めよう
Let's start from here
さーさー、みんなの声を聞かせてくれ！
Now, now, let me hear everyone's voices!
もっともっと大きい声出せるよね！
You can give me even louder voices, right?!
行きますよ！
Here we go!
声を合わせて一緒に、せーの！
Raise your voices together, and... one, two!
白上も 歌も
Let Shirakami and the songs
皆さんに届け！
reach everyone!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8!
押して押されてお兄さんもお姉さんも！
Pushing and pulling, brothers and sisters!
1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3!
ここまでよくできました。
You've done well so far.
最後に一つ。
One last thing.
3000回でも足りないぞ。
3000 times isn't enough.
100万回 愛してる！
I love you a million times!
これまでを支えてくれたさ
You've supported me until now
皆さんに寄り添いたいなって
I want to be close to everyone
大切な仲間たちとこれからも
With precious friends, from now on too
今もずっと大好きなこの場所で
Always and forever in this place I love
君も至って押したってWelcome
You're here, you're pushing, welcome
ワクワク更新中
Excitement in progress
まだ見ぬ明日も 未来も
The tomorrow and future yet unseen
お友達ですよ！
We are friends!
泣いたってしょげたって 大好きじゃい
Even if you cry or get depressed, I love you
笑顔で一緒に ハイ・ファイ・ハイ！
High-five-high together with a smile!
心を歌に重ねて
Layering our hearts on the song
届けましょう ハイ！ハイ！
Let's deliver it! High! High!
繋げましょう ハイ！ハイ！
Let's connect! High! High!
シャイニースマイル！
Shiny Smile!
さあ横浜！もっともっと盛り上がっていこうか！
Now Yokohama! Let's get even more excited!
みんな手振って声出していけますよね！
Everyone wave your hands and shout, you can do it, right?!
全力でいけますよね！
You can go all out, right?!
声が小さい！いけますよね！
The voices are small! You can do it, right?!
ありがとう。最後まで楽しんでいってください。
Thank you. Please enjoy until the very end.
閃光のように...
Like a flash of light...
いくぞ！
Let's go!
君が見てる私の世界
The world of mine that you see
歪んでいく悪戯の中で
In the midst of the distorting mischief
立ちすくむ私 言葉並べてしまったせいなのか
I'm frozen, is it because I lined up words?
少し笑えた君と共に歩んできた
I could smile a little, having walked with you
夜の果てを思い出し歌う
Remembering the end of the night and singing
言葉にならない感情事すべて今届けたい
Everything, all the feelings that can't be put into words, I want to deliver now
君が愛してくれるから君を愛してるから
Because you love me, because I love you
刹那の今が輝いてゆく
The fleeting moment of now is shining
千の星座を見上げ超新星のスピードで
Looking up at a thousand constellations at supernova speed
閃光のようにいつでも会いにゆく
Like a flash of light, I'll always go to see you
満ちてる私の未来
My future is filling up
積み重ねる引力兼ねて
Accumulating, combining gravity
様式的な現実感が曖昧になってゆく
The formal sense of reality is becoming ambiguous
そんな毎日だけどとても大事なことは
Days like that, but the very important thing
自分のことも愛せることだ
Is being able to love yourself too
多少はうまくできない時だってまたやり直そう
Even when you can't do it well sometimes, let's start over again
君が相手じゃなくたって君を愛すから
Even if you're not the one, I'll love you
刹那の今が輝いて
The fleeting moment of now is shining
千の星座を見上げ超希望のスピードで
Looking up at a thousand constellations at super-hope speed
心繋ぐ
Connecting hearts
もっともっと声出して！
Shout more and more!
まだ足りないぞ！
Still not enough!
最高！
The best!
3000回の言葉じゃ何も伝わらない
3000 words convey nothing
実はもっと間近で...
Actually, more close up...
...輝きまで
...until the radiance.
この全身全霊の一生いっぱいの感情よ 届け
May these wholehearted, lifelong emotions reach you!
君だけが愛してくれたから
Because only you loved me,
君を愛してるから
because I love you,
切なさの今が煌めいてく
the painful present is starting to sparkle.
千の星空を見上げ
Looking up at a thousand starry skies,
超新星のスピードで
at the speed of a supernova,
閃光のように 今会いにいく
like a flash of light, I'm coming to see you now.
フィアリーナにキングが帰ってきたぞ！
The King has returned to Fialina!
国民のみんな、まだ声出し足りないよね！
Everyone, you haven't shouted enough yet, have you!
いけるよね！
You can do it, right!
アリーナ！
Arena!
スタンド！
Stand!
3階！
3rd Floor!
そして今この配信を見てくれてるみんな！
And everyone watching this stream right now!
せーの！
Ready, set...
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんなー！
Everyone!
はあ、やばい、もうやばいんですけども、
Whoa, this is crazy! It's already crazy...
みなさん、改めてまして...
...Everyone, once again...
こんこんきつねー！
Konkon-kitsune!
ホロライブ1期生、ゲーマーズ兼、みんなの王様、白上フブキです！
Hololive 1st Gen & Gamers, and your King, Shirakami Fubuki!
いや、待ちに待ったこの日が、ついにやってきましたよ！
Wow, this long-awaited day has finally arrived!
うわー、すごかった、みんな、3曲連続だけど
Whoa, that was amazing. Everyone, we did 3 songs in a row but
よくついてこれましたね、すごかった、流石です！
you kept up well. It was amazing, as expected!
いやもう白上もさ、みんなの声聞きながらもう煽っていくしかねえと
I felt like I had to keep firing you up while listening to your voices.
負けじ負けじとね、みんなも声出していけーって感じで
Not wanting to be outdone, I was like "Keep those voices coming!"
ねー、もう素晴らしかったです、ありがとうございます！
It was just wonderful. Thank you very much!
ふう、ちょっとね、お水も飲みたいんですけども
Phew, I want to drink some water, but...
今日はですね、まああの、FBKINGDOM、建国祝祭みたいな感じなんですけども
Today is like the Founding Festival of FBKINGDOM...
みんな今日、FBKINGDOMに入国ってちょっと思ってませんか？
Do you all think you're "entering" FBKINGDOM today?
思ってる？もしや。
Do you? Perhaps?
いや、違うよみんな。
No, you're wrong.
ここはもうFBKINGDOMからみんなの実家だから、おかえり！
This is FBKINGDOM, which is your home, so welcome back!
そう、そうだよ、みんなは帰ってきたんだ、この国に。
That's right, exactly. You've come back to this country.
ね、ちょっともう一回やろうかみんな。
Let's do it one more time.
おかえりー！
Welcome back!
ありがとう！もっとね、この後もいっぱい歌う予定なので
Thank you! I'm planning to sing many more songs after this, so
もっとね、声たくさん聞かせてくださいね！
please let me hear your voices even more!
そしてですね、本日は、素敵な演奏でライブを盛り上げてくれる
And also, today we have
バンドメンバーたちが、いらっしゃいます！
the band members here who are livening up the concert!
かっこいい！もうね、最高の音楽ですね
So cool! It's the best music.
このフィアリーナ、全身で浴びてください、いぇーい！
Please soak up this "Fialina" with your whole body! Yay!
はい、今回のライブなんですけども、なんと海外でもね、ライブビューイングさせていただいております！
We're also having live viewings overseas for this concert!
Hi friends! 見てる？
Hi friends! Are you watching?
配信のD席のみんな！
Everyone in the online D-seats!
ライブビューイングの皆もね、Enjoy FBKINGDOM ANTHEM!
Everyone at the live viewings, Enjoy FBKINGDOM ANTHEM!
いっぱいね、最後まで見てって下さい！
Please watch until the very end!
ほう、そして、D席のみんなもよお見えとるぞい
Ho, and I can see everyone in the D-seats well too.
みんなもアピールして、ほら。
Everyone, show yourselves, come on.
会場のみんなもD席のみんなにイェーイって、イェーイ！
Everyone at the venue, say "Yay" to the D-seats! Yay!
コメントとかもしっかり見てますので
I'm also keeping a close eye on the comments, so
ちゃんと皆さん、コメントもいっぱい、いっぱいして下さいね、お願いします！
please leave lots and lots of comments. Please!
あ、それですね、ちょっと残念なお知らせがあるんですけども、
Ah, about that, I have a bit of a disappointing announcement...
しても、いいかな？
Can I say it?
残念なお知らせ！
Disappointing announcement!
えー、なんと！
Uh, what?!
無料パートをやってるんですけど、今、YouTubeとTikTokで。
We're doing a free part right now on YouTube and TikTok.
なんと、それを見ているすこん部はですね、ここまでとなります！
And for the Sukon-bu watching that, this is as far as it goes!
うわぁー！ここまでだー！
Whoa! This is the end!
はい。
Yes.
もっともっと盛り上がりたいよっていうね、
If you want to get even more pumped up...
国民のみんなは！
My fellow citizens!
チケットを買って最後まで一緒に楽しんでください！
Please buy a ticket and enjoy the rest of the show with us until the end!
お願いします！
Please do!
さてさて。
Now then.
じゃあ皆さん、まだまだね、いっぱい歌聞きたいですよね？
Well everyone, you still want to hear lots more songs, right?
うおー！まだまだ盛り上がっていけるよな？
Whoa! We can still get even more hyped, can't we?
お、なんか、ちょっとさっき歌ってる時に聞いた声より小せえぞ！
Oh, your voices are a bit smaller than what I heard when I was singing earlier!
盛り上がっていけるよな？！
We can get hyped, can't we?!
最高！
Awesome!
よし！
All right!
FBKINGDOM "ANTHEM"、楽しんでいきましょう！
FBKINGDOM "ANTHEM", let's have some fun!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!